Workona Privacy Policy
======================

_Last updated Nov 28, 2023_

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how Workona Inc. (“Workona,” “we,” or “us”) collects, uses and discloses your personal information. If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the United Kingdom (“UK”), or Switzerland, “personal information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. This Policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites, mobile applications and other online products and services where this Policy is posted (collectively, the “Service”).

We may change the provisions of this Policy at any time and will indicate when changes have been made by revising the date at the top of this Policy. Your use of the Services, or any portion thereof, following the posting of such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. We encourage you to review the Policy whenever you access the Services to make sure that you understand our information collection, use and disclosure practices. If we make material changes to this policy, we will provide you with additional notice of such changes and give you an opportunity to opt-out of the Service before using or sharing previously collected information in a materially different way.

If you are a California resident, please also review our California Resident Privacy Notice below for more information about the types of personal information we collect and disclose, as well as how to exercise your rights under California law.

### Information That We Collect

We may collect a variety of information from or about you or your devices from various sources, as described below.

If you do not provide certain information when requested, you may not be able to use our Services if that information is necessary to provide you with our Services or if we are legally required to collect it.

**A. Information That You Provide to Us**

**Registration and Profile Information.** When you register to use our Services, sign up for notifications or updates, or register for our events or promotions, we ask you for information including but not limited to your name, email address, phone number, home address and any additional information you may provide. If you sign up through a third-party site or one of our integration partners, we will receive certain information from those third parties, such as your name and account information.

**Content.** We store, process and maintain content that you create and/or upload using the Services (as well as previous versions of your content), including Workona content that you create, URLs you save, images you upload, sharing lists, and other data related to your account in order to provide the Services to you.

**Communications.** If you contact us directly, fill out surveys or request additional information, or otherwise communicate with us through our Services, we may receive your name, email address, phone number, the contents of a message or attachments that you may send to us, and other information you choose to provide.

**Careers.** If you apply for a job with us, you may submit your contact information and your resume online. We will collect the information you choose to provide on your resume, such as your education and employment experience, and the information requested through our online application questions. You may also apply through LinkedIn. If you do so, we will collect the information you make available to us on LinkedIn.

**Payment Information.** If you make a purchase through our Services, in addition to the information described above, we will collect billing address. Your payment-related information, such as credit card or other financial information, will be collected by our third-party payment processors on our behalf.

**B. Information We Collect When You Use Our Services**

**Location Information.** When you use our Services, we infer your general location information, for example, by using your internet protocol (IP) address.

**Device Information.** We receive information about the device and software you use to access our Services, including IP address, web browser type, and operating system version.

**Usage Information.** To help us understand how you use our Services and to help us improve them, we automatically receive information about your interactions with our Services like the pages or other content you view, referrer URL, number of log-ins, data displayed or clicked on (e.g., UI elements, links), actions taken through the Services, error reports and the dates and times of your visits.

**Information from Cookies and Similar Technologies.** We and our third-party partners collect personal information using cookies, pixel tags, or similar technologies. Our third-party partners, such as analytics and advertising partners, may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across different services. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to our Services. Please review your web browser’s “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept certain categories of cookies from our Services, you may not be able to utilize the features of our Services to their fullest potential. For more information about cookies and your choices, please the Your Choices section of this policy.

**Video Recording Information.** When you participate in a video conference with us, we may record the session and retain recordings of the session. When we record, you will be notified that the call is being recorded and be asked to consent.

**Course Information.** If you participate in a training or product course, we collect course completion data.

**C. Information We Receive from Third Parties**

**Information from third-party services.** If you choose to link our Services to a third-party account, e.g. one of our integration partners, we may receive information about you, including your profile information and your photo, and your use of the third-party account. If you wish to limit the information available to us, you should visit the privacy settings of your third-party accounts to learn about your options.

**Google APIs.** The use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the [Chrome Web Store User Data Policy](https://developer.chrome.com/webstore/program_policies), including the [Limited Use](https://developer.chrome.com/webstore/program_policies#limited_use) requirements. The use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.

**Other third parties.** We may receive additional information about you, such as information about your company, company size, job title, and job level as well as contact information, such as email address or phone number, from third parties such as data or marketing partners and combine it with other information we have about you. Please note that all of the information we collect about you may be combined and used for the purposes described in the “How We Use the Information We Collect” section below. If you do not provide your information when requested, you may not be able to use our Services if that information is necessary to provide you with our Services or if we are legally required to collect it.

### How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information we collect for the following purposes:

* **Analytics and Feedback:** Monitoring and evaluating trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services and collecting feedback for how to improve them.
* **Auditing Interactions:** Auditing related to your interaction with our Services and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with other standards.
* **Communicating:** Communicating with you, providing you with updates and other information relating to our services and products, providing information that you request, responding to comments and questions and requests, and otherwise providing sales and customer support.
* **Compliance:**For compliance purposes, including enforcing our terms of service, other customer contracts or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested in any judicial process or by any governmental agency.
* **Connecting Third Party Services:** Facilitating the connection of third-party services or applications, such as integrations.
* **Contracting Vendors:** Contracting with vendors and service providers to perform services on our behalf, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytics services.
* **Data Aggregation:** Aggregating information collected through our Services and using it for lawful purposes such as to see the number of users who used a type of document or shape or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement.
* **Debugging:** Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
* **Enabling Transactions:** Otherwise enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.
* **Fraud and Incident Prevention:**Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.
* **Identity verification:** Verifying identity for login purposes and to provide product support in certain situations
* **Improving Our Services:** Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of our services, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance our services.
* **Job Applications and Prospects:** Recruiting applicants for open positions and processing job applications.
* **Marketing:** Sending or showing you advertising or promotional materials, including information about new products, services, contests, features and enhancements, special offers and other events from Workona and our select partners that may be useful, relevant, valuable, or otherwise of interest to you.
* **Merging and Combining Data:** Linking or combining with other information we acquire from third parties to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.
* **Order Fulfillment:** Providing and delivering the products and Services you request, process transactions and payments, and to send you related information, including confirmations and invoices.
* **Personalization:**Personalizing your experience with our Services, such as providing content, language preference, communications or features that match user profiles or interests.
* **Providing Services:** Providing, maintaining, operating, and improving our Services.
* **Research:** Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.
* **Sales Outreach:** Contacting current or prospective users or customers to discuss our offerings.
* **Security Issues:** Finding and preventing fraud and abuse, and responding to trust and security issues that may arise.
* **Sending Messages:** Sending you text messages or push notifications.
* **Training and Rewards:** Offering training, advocacy and reward opportunities to our users.
* **Transactional Communications:** Sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages.
* **Transient Use:** Short-term, transient use.
* **Notified Purpose:** For other purposes for which we provide specific notice at the time the information is collected.

### How We Disclose the Information We Collect

We do not disclose information we collect from or about you except as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time of the collection.

* **Advertising Partners.** We work with third-party advertising partners to show you ads that we think may interest you. Some of our advertising partners are members of the Digital Advertising Alliance, the Network Advertising Initiative, or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance. If you do not wish to receive personalized ads, please visit their opt-out pages to learn about how you may opt out of receiving web-based personalized ads from member companies. You can also access any settings offered by your mobile operating system to limit ad tracking, or you can install the AppChoices mobile app to learn more about how you may opt out of personalized ads in mobile apps.
* **Affiliates.** We may disclose any information we receive to our partners, corporate affiliates, parents, or subsidiaries for any purpose described in this Policy.
* **Analytics Providers.** We use analytics services including Google Analytics to collect and process certain analytics data about our Services. These services may also collect information about your use of other websites, apps, and online resources. You can learn more about Google’s practices by visiting [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
* **Consent.** We may also disclose personal information from or about you or your devices with your permission.
* **Content, Documents, and Chat.** Content you create, upload, or copy into our products may, if you choose, be read, copied, used and redistributed by people who have access to the content. Information you disclose using the chat function of the Services may be read, copied, used and redistributed by people participating in the chat. Use care when including sensitive personal information, such as home addresses or phone numbers, in documents you share or in chat sessions. In addition, if you accept an invitation to view or collaborate on a document, your personal information may be visible to certain other users on the account (e.g. the account owner) or on the document (e.g. other collaborators).
* **Integrations and Other Online Services.**Our Services allow you to, upon your direction, integrate with other online services and disclose your documents or other information to such services. You understand and agree that the use of your information by any other service will be governed by the privacy policies of these third-party services and your settings in those services. We encourage you to review their privacy policies.
* **Marketing Services.** We do not rent, sell, or share information about you with non-affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission.
* **Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.** We may transfer or disclose your personal information to service providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a financing or corporate transaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company, or we sell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets.
* **Social Networks.** We may post user feedback or customer case studies on our social media accounts.
* **User’s Employer.** If you are a registered user, and the domain of the primary email address associated with your account is owned by your employer, and a representative of that organization requests information related to email domain users, to establish or manage an account or otherwise, then we may share certain information concerning your individual or team account with that organization, including your name and email address. Your account may also be consolidated into the organization’s corporate account.
* **Users or Registrants from Same Domain.** If you are a registered user, and the domain of the primary email address associated with your account is a corporate email domain (e.g., not a free email domain), we may share that you are a registered user with other individuals registering for or using our Services with email addresses on the same email domain.
* **Vendors and Service Providers.** We may disclose any information we receive to vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of services to us.
* **When Required by Law and Similar Disclosures.** We may access, preserve, and disclose your personal information if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: (a) satisfy any applicable law or regulation, (b) comply with law enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (c) respond to your requests; (d) protect your, our, or others’ rights, property, or safety; (e) enforce or investigate potential violations of our contract with you; or (f) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. For the avoidance of doubt, the disclosure of your personal information may occur if you post any objectionable or illegal content through our Services.

### Your Choices

* **Termination of Services.** You may terminate your use of the Services at any time, but in order for us to remove all of your information from our systems, you must permanently delete your account. After permanently deleting your account, we may retain certain information as required by law, in accordance with our back-up policy, or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of your information for a certain period of time.
* **Editing or Deleting your Personal Information.** You may update, correct, or delete information about you at any time by logging into your account and modifying your information, or by emailing us at [privacy@workona.com](mailto:privacy@workona.com). We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. If you wish to deactivate your account, please email us at [privacy@workona.com](mailto:privacy@workona.com), but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time. We will respond to your access request within 30 days. Upon request, Workona will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information that we are aware of. To request this information, contact us at [privacy@workona.com](mailto:privacy@workona.com).
* **Promotional Communications.** You may opt out of receiving promotional emails, text messages, or mail from Workona by visiting your user settings page at [https://workona.com/0/settings](https://workona.com/0/settings) and updating your communications preferences, by following the instructions in emails or text messages, or by sending an email to [privacy@workona.com](mailto:privacy@workona.com). If you opt out, we may still send you transactional or relationship messages, such as emails about your account or our ongoing business relations.
* **Do Not Track.** There is no accepted standard on how to respond to Do Not Track signals, and we do not respond to such signals.
* **Cookies.** Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Removing or rejecting browser cookies does not necessarily affect third party cookies used in connection with our Services. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. For more information about your options, please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://workona.com/policies/cookies/).

### Data Security

* Workona takes reasonable measures to protect your personal information and your spaces from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction and to ensure that your spaces remain available to you.

### Data Retention

* We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We store our backups for six (6) months. We may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

### Third Parties

* Our Services may contain links to other websites, products, or services that we do not own or operate (Third-Party Services). We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third-Party Services. Please be aware that this Policy does not apply to your activities on these Third-Party Services or any information you disclose to these Third-Party Services. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these Third-Party Services before providing any information to them.

### Children’s Privacy

* We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under 16 years of age, and no parts of our Services are directed to children. If you learn that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of this Policy, please contact us using the contact information below.

### Hosting and Data Transfer

* We are based in the United States and, unless we expressly agree otherwise, we may host, transfer, and process data, including personal information, in the United States and in other countries through Workona affiliates and third parties that we use to operate and manage the Services. These countries may have data protection laws that are different from those of your country of residence. Workona uses a variety of safeguards, including contractual and technical measures, to protect the data we transfer.
* Where required by law, we provide adequate protection for the transfer of personal information in accordance with applicable law, such as by obtaining your consent, based on European Commission-approved or UK Government-approved Standard Contractual Clauses, by relying on a European Commission, a UK Government, or Swiss Government adequacy decision, by relying on Binding Corporate Rules, or otherwise in accordance with applicable data protection laws. For more information about how we handle transfers of personal information from the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom or Switzerland, or to obtain a copy of the contractual safeguards we use for such transfers, please contact us as specified below.
* Workona complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“EU-U.S. DPF”), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF”), and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“Swiss-U.S. DPF”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Workona has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (“EU-U.S. DPF Principles”) with regard to the processing of personal information received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Workona has also certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (“Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles”) with regard to the processing of personal information received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles (together, “Principles”), the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (“DPF”) program, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/). To learn more about our certification with the DPF see here. Workona will transfer personal information to the U.S. based on Workona’s DPF certification, and will rely on its DPF certification as the primary mechanism for data transfers to the U.S. If Workona withdraws from the DPF, the DPF is invalidated, or otherwise personal information cannot be lawfully received based on the DPF, Workona will rely on appropriate European Commission-approved or UK Government-approved Standard Contractual Clauses, or otherwise transfer personal information in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
* Please direct any inquiries or complaints regarding our compliance with the above Principles to the point of contact listed in the “Contact Us” section below. If Workona does not resolve your complaint, or if Workona does not address your complaint to your satisfaction, and the complaint concerns our handling of Non-HR personal information, you may submit your complaint to JAMS, Workona’s designated alternative dispute resolution provider for DPF issues at [https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution). JAMS is located in the United States and their services are provided at no cost to you. Under certain conditions specified by the Principles, you may also be able to invoke binding arbitration to resolve your DPF related complaint. You can find further information on the DPF website. In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Workona commits to cooperate and comply respectively with the advice of the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved complaints concerning our handling of human resources data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF in the context of the employment relationship. In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Workona commits to cooperate and comply respectively with the advice of the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved complaints concerning our handling of human resources data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF in the context of the employment relationship.
* Workona is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the FTC. If Workona shares European Data with a third-party service provider that processes the data solely on our behalf, then Workona will be liable for that third party’s processing of European Data in violation of the Principles, unless Workona can prove that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.
* Under the Principles, you have the right to access your information that Workona has collected from you. You may do so by contacting Workona using the “Contact Us” information below. You have the right to limit the use and disclosure of your personal data by not providing said information to Workona or by not using our Services. You may request that Workona correct, amend, or delete your information where it is inaccurate, or has been processed in violation of the Principles, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question, or where the rights of other persons would be violated.

### California Privacy Disclosure

* Under the California Consumer Privacy Protection Act (CCPA), we are required to provide you with information about the information Workona may collect, the purpose for which we collect such information, the sources of that information, and the categories of third parties with whom we share that information.
* In the preceding 12 months, we have collected the following categories of personal information: identifiers, financial information, internet or electronic network activity information, professional and employment-related information, education information, and inferences. For details about the precise data points we collect and the categories of sources of such collection, please see the Information We Collect section above. We collect personal information for the business and commercial purposes described in the How We Use the Information We Collect section above. In the preceding 12 months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information for business purposes to the following categories of recipients:

| Category of Personal Information | Categories of Recipients |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Advertising networks, data analytics providers, payment processing and other financial services partners, fulfillment partners, security and fraud prevention partners, customer service partners, general business productivity partners and recruiting partners |
| Financial information | Payment processing and other financial services partners, fulfillment partners, security and fraud prevention partners, customer service partners |
| Internet or electronic network activity information | Advertising networks, data analytics providers, payment processing and other financial services partners, fulfillment partners, security and fraud prevention partners, customer service partners |
| Professional and employment-related information | Data analytics providers, fraud prevention partners, recruiting partners |
| Education information | Data analytics providers, recruiting partners, general business productivity partners |
| Inferences | Advertising networks, data analytics providers, payment processing partners, fulfillment partners, customer service partners |
| Other information you choose to provide | Advertising networks, data analytics providers, payment processing and other financial services partners, fulfillment partners, security and fraud prevention partners, customer service partners, recruiting partners |

Workona California Resident Privacy Notice

* California residents have the right to request access to or deletion of their personal data. You may exercise these rights as described in the “Your Choices and Rights” section above, or by emailing us at [privacy@workona.com](mailto:privacy@workona.com). California residents also have the right to request additional details about our information practices and to not be discriminated against for exercising their rights. After submitting a request to access or delete your personal data, please monitor your email address associated with your Workona account for correspondence from Workona aimed at verifying your identity before we process your request. If we receive your request from an authorized agent, we may ask for evidence that you have provided such agent with written authority to submit requests on your behalf. We may also require that you confirm your request and your identity directly with Workona.
* Workona does not sell the personal information of its users in the traditional sense (i.e., in exchange for payment). However, the CCPA defines the term “sale” very broadly, including in such a way that transfers of information relating to advertising cookies could be considered a sale. As described above and in our [Cookie Policy](https://workona.com/policies/cookies/), we may share your personal data with advertising partners so that they can show ads promoting Workona on other properties. If you are a California resident, and to the extent that any of these services are considered a “sale” of personal information under the CCPA, then you have the right to opt-out of the sale. You may opt out of the use of your information for interest-based advertising purposes as described in the “Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others” section above.

### European Economic Area and United Kingdom Disclosure

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), please review this additional information.

**Legal Basis for Processing**

When we process your personal data, we will only do so in the following situations:

* We have your consent to do so. For example, we may ask your consent to send you marketing communications.
* We need to use your personal data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the Services you have requested).
* We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to communicate with you about changes to our Services, and to provide, secure, and improve our Services.

**Your Rights**

* You have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data, including the right to access, review, modify, and delete your personal data. You may exercise your rights by following the instructions under “Your Choices” above, or by contacting us using the contact details at the end of this Policy. Before fulfilling your request, we may ask you to provide reasonable information to verify your identity. Please note that there are exceptions and limitations to each of these rights, and that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain personal information for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. In addition, certain choices may make it impossible to provide the Services. For instance, if you ask us to delete all your personal information and no exception applies, we will no longer be able to provide the Services since certain personal information, such as an email address, are needed to provide the Services. We will inform you when you will need to permanently delete your account in order to satisfy a request you have made.

**Questions or Complaints**

* If you are located in the EEA, the UK, or Switzerland, and have a concern about our processing of personal information, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, including in your country of residence, place of work, or where an incident took place.

### Contact Us

* If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact Workona at [privacy@workona.com](mailto:privacy@workona.com) or via mail at 2261 Market Street #4455 San Francisco, CA 94114, Attn: Privacy Notices.
